and
life like said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou not
make unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
the above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in a water under the
Earth thou shall not bow down thyself to
them nor serve them for the Lord thy God
I'm a jealous God visiting the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children until
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me and showing Mercy unto
thousands of them that love me and keep
my Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep be holy six days
shall thy labor and do all thy work but
the seven day is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God in it thou shall not do any work
thou nor thy son nor thy daughter thy
man's servant nor thy maid servant nor
thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the M
Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea and
all that in them is and resteth the
seventh day wherefore the Lord bless the
Sabbath day and Hollow it honor thy
father and thy mother that thy days may
be long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee thou shall not kill thou
shall not commit adultery thou shall not
steal thou sh not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou sh not cover
th neighbor's house thou not cover th
neighbor's wife nor his man's servant
nor his maid servant nor his Ox nor his
ass nor anything that is thy neighbors
ReRe Exodus 21 through1 17 and may the
Lord have a blessing to the reading of
his words in Jesus name we pray amen
amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all V questions will not be answered and
all long scripture questions will not be
answer for time sake but we may be able
to point you in the direction of a DVD
or a CD that you can purchas by calling
office so please be as direct as
possible with your questions so we can
be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just asking that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce you to family that be
be taking part in the panel this evening
we got brother
Jerome raise in peace Brother Julius
good evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother tanzel good evening
sister
Deborah good
evening and we have sister Casey with us
as well as the guest caller and I'm
brother Cornell sister Deborah what is
our first question of the
evening all right before getting into
that there are several held over Q&A
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's
Q&A uh noris tape says how were the
saakes killed during Great
Tribulation which is prior to the first
resurrection crying out to the Lord
asking how long
before they are Avenged when they were
dead all right brother Julius can you
share some light on that question
absolutely The Book of Revelation is uh
prophetically speaking of end time
prophecies so John told us uh when you
read Revelation the first chapter John
tells us that he was in the spirit on
the Lord's day and so he saw the
future so the Dead
we know that the dead don't talk but
their Works talk for them so let's go to
that scripture let's go to Revelation
the 6th
chapter Revelation chapter 6 brother
tenzel just like your works are talking
for you every day of your
life and we understand what's going on
in the world and if we should die before
the Lord come our work will
testify of how long verse n re 6 and9
let's read quick brother Revelation 6
and9 go ahead and when he had opened the
fifth seal I saw under the altar The
Souls of them that were slain for the
word of God and for the testimony which
they held he saw the dead that was slain
for the word of God and for the
testimony the uh their Works testify to
them go ahead and they cried with a loud
voice saying how long oh Lord holy and
Truth do thou not judge and avenge our
blood on them that dwell on the earth
and that was on their mind when they
when they passed away just like we know
but we already know when the Lord gonna
come at the seven trumpet let's let's
let me show you two more places real
quick where other people testified let's
go to uh uh Genesis chapter
4 Genesis chapter 4
Cain killed his brother Abel gen 4 and
pick it up at verse one Genesis 4 And1
quickly go ahead tenzel and Adam knew
Eve his wife and she conceive and bear
can and said I've gotten a man from the
Lord and she again Beed his brother Abel
and Abel was a keeper of sheep but Cain
was a teller of the ground so one was a
farmer and one was a Shepherd Abel was a
Shepherd Cain was a farmer and they
bought a sacrifice to the Lord and Cain
got jealous of his brother skip all way
down to verse uh six go
ahead and the Lord said unto Cain why
art thou Rob and why is thy continence
Fallen uhuh thou doest well shall thou
not be accepted that's the key right
there if you do well Cain or won't you
be accepted abble did well now if you do
well Cain your offering will be accepted
read and if thou doest not well sin lith
at the door and unto thee shall be his
desire and thou shall rule oh over him
continue and Cain talked with Abel his
brother and it came to pass when they
were in the field that Cain rose up
against Abel his brother and slew him go
ahead and the Lord said unto Cain where
is Abel thy brother and he said I know
not am I My Brother's Keeper uhhuh and
he said what hast thou done the voice of
thy Brothers blood cth unto me from the
ground blood don't talk but can but ab's
work spoke for him Cain went went went
evil and Abel did well one last place
Nehemiah chapter 13 let's look at
somebody else that's G to be in the
Kingdom but yet he's dead but look what
he asked of the Lord Nehemiah 13 the
book of Nehemiah
13 and when you get it brother pick it
up at verse 9 look what Nehemiah did
while he was alive go ahead and look
what he asked look go ahead Nehemiah
and9 go ahead brother then I commanded
and they cleansed the chambers and
thither brought I again the vessels of
the house of God yes the meat offering
and the
frankincense and I perceived that the
portion of the Levites had not been
given them for the Levites and the
singers that did the work were fled
everyone to his field man go ahead and
read then contended I with the rulers
and said why is the house of God
forsaken uhhuh I gathered them together
and set them in their place then brought
all Judea the ties of the Corn and new
wine and the oil unto the treasuries so
Nehemiah did all his work rebuilding the
house of the Lord and restoring the
priesthood because it had been abandoned
the house of the Lord had been abandoned
skip down to verse 14 and look at him go
ahead remember me oh my God concerning
this look what he said remember thee
remember me oh my God for the works that
I have done we know he gonna be in the
resurrection go ahead and wipe not out
my good deeds that I have done for the
house of my God and for the offices
thereof so Nehemiah is dead but his
Works testified of his works his Works
testified of him although he's dead it's
the same thing in Revelation the 6th
chapter so these Souls that cried out to
the altar is asking the Lord how long
will it be before you our blood of our
brothers is Avenged and we know that
they going to be white Rob gonna be
given to every last one of them that's
the best I can do with that
Cornel all right thank you for that hope
that answered their question next
question next question uh Stephen gugus
ask do we owe Ties on credit cards and
or when we overdraft on debit cards what
about if we receive a gift that's cash
gift card do we owe Ties on these things
all right right credit cards and cash
and guess caller do they owe Ties on
these
things no uhuh going tell you to pay TI
on all your increase so if you got a
credit card that's not an increase or a
debit card that's not an increase it's
talking about any money that come to you
other than uh uh uh you know other than
say uh that uh you borrow some money
that's not an
increase it's money that you make like
your salary or somebody give you a gift
uh you win some kind of lottery or
something that is increase credit card
and debit card no there's not an
increase that's all I have to say all
right hope that answered your question
next question sister next question Zion
says I try my best to do the
Commandments and do what God asked me to
do but it seems like everyone and
everything is against me why is it like
this I'm beginning to lose that Zeal I
used to have brother Julius help out
with that Zeal that they feel is fading
away
welcome to being a true
Christian let's go to James the first
chapter people think that when you come
into this knowledge of the true things
are going to get easier no no no no your
battle is just beginning and Jesus said
if you if any man will follow me let him
take up his cross not wear it take it up
and follow me that mean you got to be
willing to suffer and even be persecuted
and even in extreme Cas heal for your
faith let's go to James chapter one
James chapter one and begin reading my
brother tenzel at verse uh let's do
verse
two look what James said
you know starting out at verse one go
ahead and read James a servant of God
and of the Lord Jesus Christ to the 12
tribes which are scattered abroad
greeting notice how that started you a
servant of God now go ahead and read
look what's goingon to happen go ahead
my brother count it all joy when you
fall into D Temptation go ahead knowing
this that the trying of your faith
worketh patience it is your time to be
tested your faith is being tested
sisters and brothers it's not you cannot
read in the Bible where it's going to be
comfortable serving God let's go to
another place let's go to Matthew the
5th chapter Jesus said your whole war is
going to start in your household a Man's
enemy should be those of his own house
mother father sister brother and so on
Friends relatives Matthew Chapter 5
Matthew Chapter 5 brother tenzel and
begin reading at verse 10 this is the
message on the mountain Matthew 5 and
verse 10 what did Jesus
say blessed are they which are
persecuted for
righteousness for righteousness sake for
there is the Kingdom of Heaven for there
is the kingdom of heaven continue at
verse 11 blessed are ye when men shall
revile you and persecute you and shall
say all man of evil against you falsely
for my sake so it is a blessing
to go through these things because you
have been found worthy to suffer for
righteousness sake even for the gospel
sake so our uh what we ask you to do is
read Ephesians the sixth chapter for the
sake of time and it will start out count
of uh he will be strong in the Lord and
in the power of His might you have to be
strong and Gage yourself to get yourself
into this Bible read this book put on
some iog lessons and be encouraged and
be strong in the Lord and Jesus said he
that endureth until the end the same
shall be saved that's all I got brother
let me read one verse in James uh a one
verse uh verse 12 James 1 and 12 because
it say blessed is the man that endureth
Temptation yeah when he is tried he
shall receive the Crown of Life yes nor
have promised to them that love him that
is right so you got to be strong in this
M yep that's that's good scripture there
and hey like you say continue to do your
best to keep the Commandments and do
what god require and you'll be all
right okay we hope that answered your
question we moving on to the next one
yes moving on Valencia says uh can you
explain Ephesian
2100 Valencia just have Ephesians then
the number two all right Valencia
sometimes we are able to kind of
determine where you might be going with
your question but not in this case so we
ask that you please resubmit with more
detail and we'll be glad to address it
let's move on sister Deborah to our next
question yes moving on Renee Israel says
the ones that are gathered after the
three and a half tribulation to go into
the Wilderness to be taught Ezekiel 20
uh vers 35 and 38 Isaiah
111 and Revelation 7
verse4 for the rebels to be purged out
will they enter into the land talking
about the first
resurrection as Mortals or
Immortals all right will they enter into
the land well Renee you went over our
two scripture minimum but uh maximum
there but we're going to guest caller
can you weigh in after that three and a
half years of tribulation and going into
the Wilderness to be
taught
sure first thing is that everybody is
not in the every Israelite is not in the
first resurrections is going to go
through the Wilderness that's right and
and once you get in that Wilderness that
don't mean you're going to get out let's
go into Ezekiel the 20th chapter and
start reading around verse
32 when you get
there and that which
cometh go
ahead and that which cometh into your
mind shall not be at all that ye say we
will be as the Heathen as the families
of the country to serve wood and
stone and as I live sayeth the Lord God
surely with a mighty hand and with a
stretched out arm and with Fury pour out
will I rule over you and I will bring
you out from the people and will gather
you out of the countries wherein ye are
scattered with a mighty hand and with a
stressed out arm and with Fury poured
out and I will
bring and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there will
I plead with you face to face like as I
pleaded with your fathers in the
wilderness of the land of Egypt so will
I plead with you sayth the Lord God
and I will cause you to pass under the
rod I will bring you into the bond of
the
Covenant and I will Purge out from among
you the rebels and them that transgress
against me I will bring them forth out
of the country where they sourn and they
shall not enter into the land of Israel
and he shall know that I am the Lord so
that's what's going to happen if you
don't make the first
resurrection he's going to do to you the
same same thing he did with our fathers
when he brought us out of Egypt we was
in the wilderness and the people that
the uh the sin against God didn't get to
the promised land let's go into numbers
the 14th chapter and read verses 22 and
23 numbers 14 verse 22 and
okay because all the those men which
have seen my glory and my Miracles which
I did in Egypt and in the wilderness and
have tempted me now these 10 times and
have not hearkened to my
voice surely they shall not see the land
which I swear unto their fathers neither
shall any any of them that provoke me
see
it the whole thing is just like it was
then you get in the wilderness and you
rebel against God he going to purge you
and purging mean he going to kill you
right there in the wilderness and you
will never get into the
land that's all Israelites that didn't
make the first resurrection right that's
all I have to say all right so the one
yes so the ones that did make the first
resurrection were they Mortals or
Immortals if you make the first
resurrection you're
Immortal all
right First Corinthians 15th chapter
said we should not all sleep but we're
going to all be
changed yes that's
right in the first resurrection then you
are an
immortal Y and everybody got some wisdom
of God that is they
go all right hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our
next next question be alert as who do
you pray for there's a lot of scriptures
about prayers and they give Matthew 5
verse 44 1 Timothy 2 verses 1 and two
John 17 verse 9 and 10 and 20 John 9
verse
31 Proverbs 28 verse 9 and 1 Peter 3
verse2
right be alert you have went way over
our scripture maximum by four scriptures
but brother Dre is going to answer a
couple of those places for you and
brother Dre what you say yeah be alert
we we're just GNA go to the first couple
that you mentioned you can uh repost the
other questions if you want answered as
well so let's go to Matthew the 5th
chapter and we going to read verses 43
and 4 44 because that was the first that
you mentioned Matthew 5
and44 so go ahead brother when you get
that
reading ye have heard that it have been
said thou shall love thy neighbor and
hate thy enemy but I say unto you love
your enemies and bless them that curse
you and do good to them that hate you
and pray for them which despitefully use
you and persecute you right so he he's
saying
here what you heard you've heard it
said that you should love your neighbor
and hate your enemy but he said pray for
him he didn't say what to pray for him
you might want to pray that they get up
off your back you might want to pray
that the the most high God change their
heart to not be your enemy but he said
pray for him here now let's let's look
at the next one that you have here
that's first
Timothy uh the second chapter 1 Timothy
the 2 chapter verses 1 and two 1 Timothy
the 2 chapter verses 1 and two go ahead
brother
tanzel I exhort therefore that first of
all supplications prayers intercessions
and giving of thanks be made for all men
for kings and for all that are in
Authority that we may lead a quiet and
peaceful life in all godliness and
honesty yeah notice he said here that
prayers be made for all men why that we
may lead a quiet and peaceful life in
goodness and in honesty nothing wrong
with that now the other ones that you
talked
about Jesus praying to the father saying
that he don't pray uh for for the world
he pray for those that's that follow him
that is in his word but we'll deal with
those if you want to repost it and talk
about it uh that's all I got on that
brother Corell all right well thank you
for that brother and uh we have to keep
that LA on the books because we have a
lot of questions that we need to get to
all right sister Deborah our next
question uh next question I Chuck arar
ask are we supposed to participate in or
watch the Olympics knowing that origin
has to do with worshiping a Greek god
can our children participate in these
activities and other events that are
similar all right brother Jerome what
you say I know I watched the little
Olympics well well the Lord say I pray
that you take them not out of the world
but that you keep them from the evil you
know understand we living among the we
living among the
Gentiles and um when you consider the
names for example that the Gentiles have
given the days of the weeks or the names
that he that they've given the months
they Pagan names but that don't mean
that we cease from doing our uh daily
weekly activity or activities through
the month because the Gentiles gave the
days of the weeks and the month Pagan
names on the same token when you talk
about the Olympics it's all right to uh
enjoy the Olympic Games you know or to
participate in Olympics of course you
don't want to be breaking the Sabbath
okay and what you want to do is just
don't get involved in their R Pagan
rituals or or ceremonies but it's all
right to watch the uh Olympic Games and
P participate in them just don't break
the Sabbath that's all I got
on all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered their question sister
Deborah our next question next question
explain first John 2 verse
19 first John 2 and verse 19 brother
Julius what you say let's go there
tenzel first Timothy um first John
two and 19 this is end time prophecy we
are in the last days the end time or the
latter times and this is a prophecy
that's been happening and has
increasingly
happened two and 19 first John two you
know what let's start at 18 let's get
the gist of this go ahead and let's date
this go
ahead little children it is the last
time and as ye have heard that in Christ
shall come but even now are there many
Antichrist whereby we know that it is
the last time so now John is explaining
we in the last days and we're talking
about people that understand truth
understand uh the word of God and then
just leaveing their faith they lose
their faith or they're drawn away that's
why the book said there are many
Antichrist go ahead and read the
19 they went out from us they left they
left from us they went out from us go
ahead but they were not of us uhuh if
they had been of us they would no doubt
have continued with us uhhuh but they
went out that they might be made
manifest that they were not all of us so
now they might be in a church or they
might be in some kind of truth but for
one reason or another some disagreement
or the way things are going they see
things differently so they leave out and
the Lord said he leave out to make them
manifest or to make them known let's go
to First Timothy the 4th chapter because
Judas was a disciple and he ended up
betraying
Jesus First Timothy he was a did Miracle
did some signs you know carried the
money back but he betrayed
Jesus First Timothy to fulfill prophecy
1 Timothy 4 and we going 1 and two First
Timothy 41-2 go ahead brother now the
spirit speaketh expressively that in the
latter time some shall depart from the
faith giving he to seduc and spirit and
doctrines of devils so now here it is
again the same thing again in the latter
times th shall depart from the faith
giving heed to seducing spirits and
doctrin of devil they gonna be drawn
away for whatever reasons go ahead at
verse two speaking lies and hypocrisy
having there conscience sear with the
hot iron in other words they leave out
and they lose all reason they lose all
sense then they start calling the church
that they came out uh blasphemers and
false prophets and so on and so forth
that they might be known
manifest that mean that God has revealed
them to us so therefore this is what's
this is what this scripture means they
went out from us but they were not of us
but had they stayed with us they would
have they would had they been of us in
truth they would have stayed with us
somebody's got to fulfill the negative
end of Prophecy anybody else want to add
right positive side is the way to be
brother Julius yes
sir all right I hope that answered your
question is we move on to our next one
yes for Ephesians 4 vers
29-31 please
explain all right let us go there that
Ephesians 4
verse 29 through
31 let's go there brother
tanzel and go right
ahead let no corrupt communication
proceed out of your mouth but that which
is good to the use of edifying that it
may Minister grace to the hearers all
right so no corrupt communication you
know you should be careful what you say
that mouth is a unruly evil full of
deadly poison go give account of every
word so all of that cursing even people
that preach against the truth that's
corrupt communication coming out of
their mouth go ahead brother and grieve
not the holy spirit of God whereby ye
are sealed unto the day of redemption
yeah don't grieve the holy spirit of God
Hey Brother Julius angels are always
watching aren't they hey we we entertain
Angels unawares yes sir verse 31 because
this right here can make you use some of
that um filthy communication and get you
in trouble too these things go ahead
brother but let all bitterness and wrath
and anger and clamore and evil speaking
be put away from you with all malice y
with all malice sometimes that intent to
harm you can really do some damage to
some people that's why Lord say Hey you
have to be sometime quick to forgive and
stay your distance if that's what quir
turn over to Colossians 3 Colossians the
chapter and let's deal a little bit with
the um filthy um the things that should
not be coming out of our mouth
Colossians 3 pick it up at verse um
eight because the Lord GNA tell us again
about these things that can come out of
your mouth and get you in trouble verse
eight brother go ahead but now ye also
put off all these anger wrath malice
blasphemy filthy communication out of
your mouth yeah filthy communication out
of your mouth that we just got through
Reading in that Ephesians now turn back
last place let's go to Exodus the 23rd
chapter Exodus
23rd and when you get there brother we G
pick it up at that at that verse
20 because we're going to read
about some people that grieve that Holy
Spirit and shown up got in trouble
Exodus
23 and pick it up at verse 20 go ahead
behold I sent an angel before thee to
keep thee in the way and to bring thee
into the place which I have
prepared so beware of him and obey his
voice provoke him not for he will not
pardon your transgression for my name is
in him so that's one of the ways this
was shown here that they did provoke
that Holy Spirit of the Lord because
they didn't want to walk in them holy
words to God and provoked the angel and
got their selves in trouble so that
gives you some of that explanation on
aians
4:29 through 31 and that's all I
got and we hope that that answered your
question sister Deborah time check as we
move on yes the time is 806
uh the next
question how should someone handle an
individual friend for many years that is
now lying in being
deceptive so guess call I need hand
somebody no matter how long you've been
knowing them when they start being lying
and being deceptive
guess caller you with
us yeah I said go and tell them that
they'll lie under
thece okay all right we didn't uh yeah
go
ahead no that's enough oh okay so tell
them that and you know God hat
all if they continue break off
relationship with her
yeah that's what the book said is say if
you got all with your brother you go to
him and you tell him that alt you got
with yeah that's right that's sir that
is
correct okay we hope that answered your
question sister Deborah next
one yes next question why did Jesus
speak in parables in Matthew 13
verse1 brother Jerome why was that
uh let's go and read it Matthew
13:10 you get it go
ahead and the disciples came and said
unto him why speakest thou unto them in
Parables now if we connect the ninth
verse and read it to the 11 excuse me it
give you some understanding of why he
spoke in
Parables go ahead and
read who have ears to hear Let Him hear
and the disciples came and said unto him
why speakest thou unto them in Parables
and he answered and said unto them
because it is given unto you to know the
mysteries of the kingdom of heaven but
to them it is not
given skip down to verse
um 13 cuzz see it was given to them to
know cuz they receiving the words and
believing and walking in it so it's
given to them to know but if you read
verse
13 you got the ones that don't want to
hear you know so it's going to be a
parable to them because they refuse to
open their ears and open their eyes to
the truth verse
13 there therefore speak ey to them to
to them in Parables because they seeing
see not and hearing they hear not
neither do they understand yeah you know
that's all I got on yeah that's right
brother because at verse 16 say blessed
are our eyes for we see and our ears for
we hear that's a
blessing yes sir thank you for that we
moving on
sister moving on who is the Angel angel
of God's presence mentioned in Isaiah
63:
7-9 who is this Angel brother
Dre I want to answer that question but
you know I'm I'm still thinking about
the question number six be alert ask and
the second passage I went to which was
uh 1 Timothy the 2 chapter verses 1 and
two and and I just want to address
something there and bring a little bit
more clarity to
it can you read that first Timothy the
second chapter verses one and two one
more time uh brother
tanzel uh First Timothy secondy yeah one
yes sir Paul and Apostle of Jesus Christ
by the will of God according to the
promise of life which is in Christ Jesus
hey tanzel 1 Timothy 1 Timothy 2 chapter
verses 1 and
two go ahead brother I ex you right the
prayer
okay I exort therefore that first of all
supplication prayers intercession and
giving of thanks be made for all men for
kings and for all that are in authority
that we may lead a quiet and Peaceable
life in all godliness and honesty
now a lot of some people don't want to
pray for this country but they live here
so let's go to Jeremiah the 29th chapter
and I want you to read Verses 4 to7 and
this is why this is important to do
Jeremiah 29 verses
4-7 go ahead and read it when you get it
brother thus sayth the Lord of hosts the
god of Israel unto all th carry away
captives whom I have caused to be
carried away from Jerusalem unto
Babylon build ye houses and dwell in
them and plant Gardens and eat the fruit
of them and keep wives and beg got sons
and daughters and take wives for your
sons and give your daughters to husbands
that they may bear sons and daughters
that ye may be increased there and not
diminished
mhm and see the Peace of the city
whether I have caused you to be carried
away captive and pray unto the Lord for
it for in the peace thereof shall ye
have peace he said pray unto the Lord
for that peace but in that peace you
gonna have some peace so it is important
to do that now uh that question who is
the Angel of God's presence and I think
Isaiah
63 is the passage so let's go to Isaiah
63 verses
7-9 Isaiah 63 verses
7-9 go ahead and read it when you get it
brother I will mention the loving
kindness of the Lord and the Praises of
the Lord according to all that the Lord
have bestowed on us and the great
goodness towards the house of Israel
which he have bestowed on them according
to his mercies and according to the
multitude of his loving
kindness but he said surely they are my
people children that will not
lie so he was their
savior go ahead and in all their
Affliction he was afflicted and the
angel of his presence saved them in his
love and in his pity he redeemed them
them and he be them and carried them all
the days of
old now let's go to to Luke the first
chapter and we gonna read about this the
angel of the Lord's presence here now
Luke the first chapter
and
uh we're gonna talk about Zacharias who
was the the priest that burned
incense in the temple and this is what
happened with with him okay so start at
verse five brother and we'll get right
down to it in a second go
ahead and there was in those days of
Herrod the King of Judea and a certain
priest named Zacharias of the cour of
abah and his wife was of the daughters
of Aaron and her name was Elizabeth go
ahead and they were both righteous
before God walking in all the
Commandments and ordinance of the Lord
blameless skip down to verse 11
and there appear unto him an angel of
the Lord standing on the right side of
the altar of
incense and when Zachariah saw him he
was troubled and Fe fear fell upon Him
skip down to verse 18 now and Zachariah
said unto the angel whereby shall I know
this for I am an old man and my wife
well stricken in years oh Angel told
Zachariah that him and his wife is going
to have a son he said why how shall I
know this CU I'm well stricken in years
go
ahead and the angel answering said unto
him I am Gabriel that stand in the
presence of God and and am sent to speak
unto thee and to show thee these Glad
Tidings this angel that stands in the
presence of God his name is Gabriel he
said I am Gabriel that stand in the
presence of God so I hope that that
helped that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question next
question all right the next question is
from Sanders Haring he says he need uh
some understanding of this verse Hebrews
10 verse
26 receive the knowledge of the truth a
person knows the truth trying to repent
from the old man but has not yet been
baptized into Jesus remain it no more
sacrifice for
sins okay well let's go to Hebrews um
10 and he talking about that verse 26
there let's read 26 and 27
and then we can um open it up to the
panel go ahead tenzel when you're
there well if we s willfully after that
we have received the knowledge of the
truth there remain of Norm more
sacrifice for
sins but a certain fearful looking forth
judgment and fiery indignation which
shall Devour the
adversaries all right so that's talking
about the Lake of Fire there that if you
sin willfully you know what right is but
you just love to keep doing wrong hey
you might end up paying that ultimate
price which is that Lake of Fire but he
was asking also about uh repenting and
be baptized right
Deborah uh that was a part of the
question he ask for some understanding
on the verse yes and he said that people
had not been baptized in the Jesus but
let let's go see what Peter said in Acts
two because the Lord didn't just put the
baptism on the table for nothing when
you know what the truth is and you know
that that brings you under the blood of
Jesus and into a covenant with him
what's the delay if you know better but
let's let's read that acts two and pick
it up at that verse
36 and then read 38 brother tanzel go
ahead so therefore let all the house of
Israel know ass surely that God have
made that same Jesus whom you have
crucified both Lord and Christ he died
for the sins of the whole world what did
Peter say in
38 then Peter said unto them repent
repent and be baptized every one of you
in the name of Jesus Christ for the
remission of sins and ye shall receive
the gift of the Holy Ghost
39 for the promise is unto you and to
your children and to all all that are
far off even as many as the Lord Our God
shall
call so repenting and baptized is they
go hand in hand open to the panel
anybody
else there's some situ it it depends and
what I mean by that is I was thinking
when I used to minister uh in the
prisons and the prisoners a lot of times
that were in the truth bleeding Jesus
you know know trying to repent and live
a Godly life but they didn't have access
to uh getting baptized and the Lord know
that so if they happen to you know pass
away before receiving it you know that's
a situation where the Lord may show them
Mercy because they didn't get baptized
but but the
sacrifices that we reading in that verse
uh in that Hebrews 10 I think the Lord
was talking about the animal sacrifice
we not under that no more and if you sin
and
willfully uh the blood of Jesus ain't
going to cover you either you know but
it depends on the situation and that's
why I was giving you an example about
the prisoners you know anybody else want
to add something
else I I saw something online about
people in prison that put a plastic bag
in a garbage can filled it up with water
and they were baptized and brothers in
prison oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and and you
hoping that they all have that you know
in mind to do that you know yeah
yeah all
right sister Deb we gonna move to our
next question with a Time Check Yes the
time is a20 he Al so as the word
heathen according to iog teaching means
Nations explain please St Matthew 18
verse1
17 all right word
heathen yeah means means other
nations other than Israel but also let's
go there and read that Matthew 18 and
verse
17 because a heathen can can also be one
that
don't practice
no Christianity no serving God the true
and living God but let's read that 18
Matthew 18- 17 go ahead
brothers and if he shall neglect to hear
them tell it unto the church but if he
neglect the heal the church let him be
unto thee as a heathen man and a
Publican all right so this a brother in
a situation here but if he don't want to
hear thee then you're supposed to take
him to two or more because in the mouth
of two or more witnesses is a fact
established so Heathen here but let's go
turn back to Leviticus 25 get a little
more clarity on that word heathen here
Leviticus 25 Leviticus
25 y we gon read out 25 and 26 I want
you to read the last verse of uh 25
which is verse 55 let's see who are we
talking about here go ahead for unto me
the children of Israel are servants they
are my servants whom I brought forth out
of the land of Egypt I am the Lord your
God so it's the Lord here talking and
he's saying that hey he brought out the
children of
Israel and they are to serve him now go
straight into that Leviticus 26 and pick
it up one and let's see go ahead it
shall make you no Idols nor Graven image
neither rear you up a standing image
neither shall you set up any image of
stone in your land to bow down unto it
for I am the Lord your God because other
nations was already doing this read he
shall keep my sabbaths and reverence My
Sanctuary I
am if you walk statues and keep my
Commandments and do them yeah then I
will give you rain in due season and the
land shall yield her increase and the
Trees of the field shall yield their
fruit the Lord was telling about you
keep his commandment all these blessings
was F to come down for you skip down to
verse 27 because it's always another
side to the coin go ahead
brother and if you shall not for all
this hearken unto me but walk contrary
unto me uhhuh I will walk contrary unto
you also in Fury and I even I will chase
chastise you seven times for your sins
yes we're going through that now but
skip down read that verse 33 that be the
last go ahead and I will scather you
among the heathens and among the Heathen
that's the other nations that the Lord
say he was going to scatter us Among Us
who is pick it up at the top of that and
I will scatter you among the heathens
and will draw out a sword after you and
your land shall be desolate and your
cities waste we long way from home and
we are amongst the Heathen that's right
every nation all the to the Four Corners
the Lord has scattered us perfectly
according to his word like he said he
would do that's all I got I like your
weigh in on it yes
sir because uh there are people that
saying that he mean uncp and all that oh
let's read a few more scripture let's go
into Malachi 1 And1 yes sir Mal Malachi
1 and
okay for from the rising of the sun even
to the going down of the same my name
shall be great among the
Gentiles in every place inance shall be
offered unto my name and a pure offering
for my name shall be great among the
Heen sayth the Lord of
hosts now if the lord's name is great
among the Heathen how they how how they
how they unou people right correct he
have
name let's go let's go to uh second
Samuel chapter
22 read uh uh uh uh
23 and the
25 2 Samuel 22
start at
23 for all his judgment were before me
and as for his statues I did not depart
from them I was also upright before him
and have kept myself from my iniquity
therefore the Lord have recompensed me
according to my righteousness according
to my cleanness in his
eyesight with the merciful thou will
show thyself merciful and with the
upright man thou will show thyself self
upright with the pure thou will show
thyself pure and with the forward thou
will show thyself unsaving and The
Afflicted people thou will save but
thine eyes are upon the halty that thou
mayest bring them down for thou are my
for thou art my lamp oh Lord and the
Lord will lighten my darkness for by
Thee I have run through a Troth by my
God have I leap over a wall
as for God his way is perfect and the
word of the Lord is tried he is a
bucklet to all them that trust in him
yes for who is God say the Lord and who
is a rock Save Our God God is my
strength and power and he maketh my way
perfect he maketh my feet like Hinds
feet and Seth me upon my high places he
teaches my hands to War so that a bowl
of Steel is broken by my arms thou has
also given me the shield thy salvation
and thy gentleness have made me great
thou has enlarged my steps under me so
that my feet did not slip I have pursued
my enemies and destroyed them and turn
not again until I have consumed them and
I have consumed them and wounded them
that they could not arise yeah they are
Fallen under my feet for thou H has G me
with strength to battle them that rosed
up against me thou Hast subdued unto me
thou has also given me the neck of my
enemies that I might destroy them that
hate me and they looked but there was
none to say even unto the Lord but he
answered them not then did I beat them
as small as the dust of the earth I did
stand them as the mire of the streets
and did spread them abroad thou also
have delivered me from the striving of
my feet people th have kept me to be
head of the Heathen a people which I
knew not Shall Serve
me okay so kept me to be the head of the
Heathen how is he the head of how's he
going this talking about Jesus here how
is he going to be the head of the
Heathen and they some unco people did
you finish
45 uh that was
44 oh go ahead strangers shall submit
themselves unto me
as soon as they hear they shall be
obedient unto
me
he not we're going to go two other
places and that's it let's go into
Galatians the first chapter and read
verses 15 and 16 did you guest caller
did you want that verse 50 or
no what did it say read it read that
verse 501 therefore I will give thanks
unto thee Oh Lord among the heathens and
I will sing praises unto thy
name okay so let let you know that's
among the Nations but skip down to
Galatians
1 and read verses 15-
16 sorry about
that go ahead
brother but when it pleases God who
separate me from my mother's womb and
called me by his grace to reveal his son
in me that I might preach him among the
Heathen immediately I confered not with
flesh and
blood
now Paul was Apostle to the Gentiles
wasn't he that's
right picked him to go out and teach
preach him among the
Heathen right Galatians 3 it's the last
place galatian 3 7 and
8 know ye therefore that they which are
of Faith the same are the children of
Abraham and the scripture foreen that
God would justify the heathens through
faith preached before the gospel unto
Abraham saying in the shall All Nations
be
blessed okay so is going to justify the
Heathen how through the blood of Jesus
because he told Abraham and his seed
shall all the nations of the earth be
blessed so you un person how can you be
uh uh uh
blessed
right the Nations there just another
name for Nations that are not Israelites
that's
right yeah Lord say it's hard desires
that all would repent and come into the
knowledge of God and that's the original
definition of Heathen biblically
speaking non-jewish
uhhuh that's
itra Israelite non
Israelite all right thank you for that
hope that answered their question next
one sister debah I believe we have
covered all of our held over
questions uh yes and the time is
8:31 we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday August the 21st
2024 daughter of Judah asks in Matthew 5
verse 17 even though Christ himself said
he didn't come to destroy the law but to
fulfill many pastors and Christians
believe that the word fulfill means the
law was done away or ended what is the
biblical definition fulfilled in this
verse what law was Christ referring to
all right brother Jerome we know the law
is not done away with or ended what you
got
brother now it definitely don't mean in
in that case okay it means to perform to
do you know I want to give you an
example uh can we go to
um Matthews third
chapter go to Matthew's the thir
chapter and let's pick it
up a
minute pick it up at the 13 read to the
15 where then cometh Jesus From Galilee
to Jordan unto John to be baptized of
him but John forbath him
saying have need to be baptized of thee
and cometh thou to
me and Jesus answered and said unto him
suffer it to be so now for thus it
becometh us to fulfill all
righteousness yeah so fulfill that's
just I'm just give you an example of the
definition of fulfill right here as well
you know it don't mean to end either it
mean to perform it right you know can we
go to that Luke Luke 4
Corel um yeah I didn't know Jerome do
you have another place you wanted to go
um well we got a um another question
that uh that's a part of this where it
says what law was Christ referring to
okay yeah but uh
if jul go ahead let him go ahead and go
to that verse and then go and deal with
this second question Luke 4 Julius what
verse Luke 4 and verse 18 to get to the
point Luke 4 and8 my apologies bro Luke
4 and8 when Jesus came from being
tempted of the devil then he came into
the
synagogue 18 tzel go ahead and
read the spirit of the Lord is upon me
because he have anointed me to preach
the gospel to the poor he has sent me to
heal the broken hearted to preach
Deliverance to the captive and
recovering the sight of the blind to set
at Liberty them that are
bruised and to preach the acceptable
year of the Lord so he was reading the
book of Isaiah of everything that he
came to do skip down to verse 21 and
this is GNA point out a piggy back off
of Jerome statement to perform go ahead
at
21 and he began to say unto them this
day is this scripture fulfilled in your
ear
so that's pertaining to what Jesus came
to
do perform
okay brother Jerome back with you yes
yes now the other question is what law
was Christ referring
to well you know what um is this this
all is coming off of Matthew 5:1
17 yes yeah because I I never read it
that's that was the thing yeah we um I
think Jerome was going to were you going
there now
brother in Matthew 5 and 17 goad you can
read it you can read it okay okay think
not that I am come to destroy the law
the prophets I have not come to destroy
but to fulfill yeah yeah so that's what
julus and myself was establishing what
fulfill means there and we were both
giving you examples of the word
fulfilled can also mean to perform it
also means to end but right there in the
verse that you gave in that question it
don't mean to end there it means to
perform
yeah
tanel the other question was um what was
that second question um what law was
Christ referring to yeah and the law
he's referring to is the laws that he
gave to Moses the laws the statutes and
the ordinances that he gave to Moses
okay um and for the sake of
time um you can go to uh Matthews I
believe uh I believe it's the uh 22nd
chapter where it tells you on these two
laws uh hang all the law and the
prophets yeah love your neighbor as love
God all your heart mind soul and
strength and love your neighbor as
yourself um guest caller you want to add
something I think what they referring to
when Jesus said come not to change but
fulfill I uh uh I think it was in a
different light you know people run they
don't have to do nothing because Jesus
fulfilled the law right but Jesus
fulfill uh everything that was written
about him yes and this question
so the direct answer to that is in Luke
okay go to Luke 24th chapter and read
verse
25 24 and
25 this going to answer the question
directly and then we're going to skip
once we read
25 what was that Luke Luke what Luke 4
and
Luke 24 and
25 uhhuh and he said verely I say unto
you no Prophet is accepted in his own
country you're in Luke
24 Luke
uhhuh
okay verse
25 then he said unto them oh fools and
slow of heart to believe all that the
prophets have spoken ought not Christ to
have suffer these things and to enter
into his
glory now so these guys was talking
about they didn't know they thought
Jesus was going to be the one and he's
going to deliver but the Bible said that
he going to get cut off right
he slow to believe all that the prophet
say uh uh I not read that one more time
then we're going to skip to let you know
he's talking about what he have to do
right ought not Christ to have suffered
these things
and to enter into his
glory uhhuh the prophet wrote that skip
down to verse uh
um down to uh uh uh
[Music]
verse let's
see verse 44
now and he said un and he said unto them
these are the words which I spake unto
you while I was yet with you that all
things must be fulfilled
which were written into the law in the
law of Moses and in the prophets and in
Psalms concerning
me see all that's written he said
concerning him that's what he came to
fulfill that's even when he was on the
cross and before he could die he uh uh
uh uh he said I thirst they put vinegar
up his mouth when he drank the vinegar
then he died why did it have to happen
like that because Prophet said that they
gave him vinegar for his drink
M he was on the cross he said my God my
God why Thou forsaken me why did he say
that because in Psalm 22nd chapter he
said my God my God why Thou forsaken
thee so he came to fulfill everything
that was written about him just like he
just said at this 44th
verse that's what that really is talking
about
don't all right Jesus did his part now
let us do
ours okay next question yes next
question uh TX Domino asked in first
Timothy 1 verses 1 through five what
should we gather from those
verses all right want go to and take a
look brother Tel and the guest caller
share some light from there 1 Timothy 1
and verse one
1 Timothy 1 and
one Paul and Apostle of Jesus Christ by
The Commandments of God our savior and
the Lord Jesus Christ which is Our
Hope read the first five that's what she
answer one to five go ahead unto Timothy
unto Timothy my own son in the faith
grace mercy and peace from God our
father in Jesus Christ our Lord as I
besought Thee to abide still at Ephesus
when I went into Macedonia that thou
mayest charge some that they teach no
other Doctrine neither give heed to
fables and endless genealogies which
Minister's question rather than Godly
edifying which is in faith do so do now
the end of the Commandment is Charity
out of a pure heart and of a good
conscience and of faith unin
now Paul is telling Timothy you know
don't get off in a whole bunch of loose
talk and Fable and we're going to let
Paul answer
himself go to First Timothy the 6th
chapter read verses 3 through 6 and Skip
down to
20 First Timothy 6 pick it up in verse
three okay
If any man Teach otherwise and consent
not to Wholesome words even the words of
our Lord Jesus Christ into the doctrine
which is according to Godliness he is
proud knowing nothing but doubting about
questions and strife of words whereof
cometh Envy Strife r evil and
surmising perverse disputing of men of
corrupt minds and destitute of the truth
supposing that gain his godliness from
such withdraw
thyself so he talk people that running
their mou getting off in the geology and
they ain't dealing with no
scripture you know back away from them
people read skip down to verse 20 and
read
it oh Timothy keep that which is
committed to thy trust avoiding profane
the vain babbling and opposition of
science falsely so-called
avoid all that kind of stuff you know
one other place second
Timothy second
chapter read verse 14
first of these things put them in
remembrance Charing them before the Lord
that they strive not about words to no
Prophet but to the subverting of the
hearers
so you know don't don't don't be off in
there using words as a servant of God
that don't make no profit what you're
doing is you subverting the people that
hearing you skip down to verse 16 and
read but Shan profane in vain babbling
for they will increase into more
ungodliness and their
work you finish that 16th verse
yeah you know what what what is vain
babbling talking about something that
don't mean nothing either you going to
be off in the uh like a lot of brothers
talking about uh uh stuff that you can't
read out of the Bible That's vain
babbling all they going to do is
increase argument one last place verse
23 but foolish and unlearned questions
avoid knowing that they do Ginger
Stripes so that's all Paul was saying to
Timothy don't get involved a whole lot
of nonsense a whole L of babbling the
whole lot of genealogy and all that
stuff you know like we got this group
talking about you know what's uh the 12
tribes of Israel is in this hemisphere
they thrw in the the Mexicans and the
Puerto Rican and the uh uh
uh Native American that's that's
genealogy vain genealogy they they can't
prove that in fact it is straight up lie
so that's phone is telling you it's all
have to say all right
hope that answered your question sister
Deborah time check is we moving along
yes time is
845 uh eyewitness says a beautiful
sermon a few weeks ago on the parable of
the sore my question is are these
permanent or temporary conditions should
you know which condition you are already
and can you do anything to combat the
first three
examples yes call them what you
say well I said it speaks for you know
you hear the word and you turn away from
it then you
know then you know that uh uh uh you
heard it by the wayside time you hear
something you hear some truth somebody
come up and contradict it and you don't
go in the Bible and check it out then
they take it away from
you and then and then a lot of time then
you hear the word of God and you go and
talking to somebody and then all of a
sudden they come down on you call you
you're in a cult and and you know and
where do you get that from and uh they
give you some opposition then you don't
talk about it no
more and the third one is it fall among
Thorns that mean that you hear the word
of God but you too busy trying to make
money running about worldly
things it's all that simple you know
either get choked out either get taken
it from you or either soon as you uh
suffer a little opposition you pull away
from it you haven't taken any root
that's all it's
saying if you listen to the lesson it
speaks for
itself
right all right thank you for that
sister debor next question
yes Nicholas toer says I heard Caucasian
came from
japet I thought Caucasians was Esau so
who are the emites in this
time and not Caucasian open to
the
panel TN brother TN brother
25 and read from 19 to
26 Genesis 25 when you get there brother
tanzel pick it up at that 19 and go on
down to
right and these are the generation of
Isaac Abraham's son Abraham beg got
Isaac and Isaac was 40 years old when he
took Rebecca to wife the daughter of
Bethel the Syrian of pan panoram the
sister of lean the Syrian and Isaac
entreated the Lord for his wife because
she was Barren and the Lord was
entreated of him and Rebecca his wife
conceived and the children struggled
together within her and she said if it
be so why am I thus and she went to
inquire of the Lord and the Lord said
unto her two nations are in thy womb
and two manner of people shall be
separated from thy bows and the one
people shall be stronger than the other
people and the Elder Shall Serve the
younger and when her days to be
delivered were fulfilled behold there
were twins in her womb and the first
came out red all over like a hairy
garment and they called his name
Esau and after that came his brother out
and his hand took hold on Esau's heel
and his name was called Jacob and Isaac
was three score years old when she Beed
them so now Esau is our twin brother he
is a
Hebrew Y and we are Hebrew Israelites
yes when brother so how can he be a
gentile or a Caucasian he just look
white right but
he is our twin
brother possibly be a a gentile or
Caucasian that's all I have to say all
right
sister go ahead yes so the
ccas came from
jet that's
right is
the Y run it all the way down there
Genesis 10 all right hope that answered
your question sister Deborah time is
getting away but next one yes Ben Elf
asked is there
um is there any Scripture to indicate
why God chose
Judah and the southern Kingdom of all
the 12 tribes is it because he knew
there be the strongest and the most
[Music]
obedient open to the
P he didn't choose
Judah he choose
David and let's go and uh uh let's go
have a look at
it let's go into uh 1
Samuel 13th chapter and read verse 14
1 Samuel
[Music]
13 verse 14 when you get there
Brothers but now thy kingdom shall not
continue and the Lord have sought him a
man after his own heart and the Lord
have commanded him to be Captain over
his people because thou has not kept
that which the Lord commanded thee
well keep reading I must that's thir 1
Samuel the 13th
chapter verse
14 yeah so they wanted to show that did
they read David maybe maybe I left
something off show you who is the after
his own
heart search
okay I don't know how I blew that search
mode one you Brothers got that
yet man after God's Own
Heart that's step 14 1 Samuel 13 1
Samuel 13 it's in that 14th verse okay
is David's there did he call the name of
David no he didn't call David is David
name is not in there but okay well let's
go and find out then let's go to acts
then
yeah acts 13
right yeah verse
22 okay read it
acts 13:22
T and when he had removed him he raised
up unto them David to be their King to
whom also he gave testimony and said I
have found David the son of Jesse a man
after my own heart which shall fulfill
all my
will so he didn't choose Judah he to
chose David and
uh and David come out of the tribe of
Judah that's why every time we talk to
tribe of Judah or talk about The Throne
he say it's David's Throne know how many
no matter how many generation pass even
when Jesus come it tells you that he
going to sit on David's Throne right not
that stronger not that he was preferred
it's just that God found David a man
after his own Hardies that mean you
think like me so David was the one that
was chosen he just happened to be out of
the tribe of
Judah he was chosen because God sa
things like me a man after my own heart
all have to say all right hope that
ansed your question sister Deborah
another question or two is time is
running out yes he also asked in Isaiah
43 verse 28 when Jacob and Israel is
referred to am I correct that it is
referring to the Southern and Northern
kingdoms respectful
respectively it's confusing because I
normally think Jacob and Israel will be
the same people but it doesn't appear
that way here and they want to know also
what does reproaches
mean all right Jacob and Israel are the
same one the Lord got Jacob and change
his name cuz somebody find that right
quick but lord said you should no longer
be called
Jacob that's a
Genesis
yes Genesis the uh
20 and then guest caller that previous
question guest caller was Psalm 8920
where he said I have found David Ezekiel
I mean Genesis 32 and 28 32
yeah okay Genesis 32 all right read that
Genesis 32 tanzel that time is getting
away from us and
uh you want to pick it up with Jacob
wrestled or you want to get straight
down to the name
change to the name change all right um
skip down and read that uh verse 27
can and he said unto him what is thy
name and he said Jacob and he said that
name shall be called No More Jacob but
Israel for as a prince has thou power
with God and with men and has
prevailed so Jacob and Israel is the
same and just that the Lord Chang his
name from Jacob to
Israel is that
it uh and what does reproaches mean in
uh Isaiah 43 verse
28 word reproach means shame disgrace
and you know uh uh
disgraced okay yeah Lord
okay yeah he was say disgrace by
throwing us into
captivity because of our
Behavior okay yeah all right sister
devil let's move to our next one yes uh
uh doc Mar Martin says can you you
please explain Matthew
25 the goat and the sheep in the world
of sports and entertainment I notice
some men are referred to as the goats
greatest of all time because this be a
form of bat forat or M bat for or
wichcraft
worship and can you explain Colossians
1: 15 and 16
is this saying the
principalities and Thrones are put in by
God I'm asking this because does our
vote really count and yes I do
vote so the first question is talking
about the goat and the Sheep is this
witcraft using the goat and the
Sheep No is just the righteous and the
wicked
right the the goat is the one that
breaks his Commandments and statutes and
the Sheep are the one that keep them
right and and that and that greatest of
all time that's some un flesh and blood
man that's just some Man created they
considered uh Dominique dos who was in
the Olympic who got seven medals they
consider her to be the greatest of all
times which spells goat you can look at
Serena Williams with the golf she I mean
the tennis she considered to be one of
the greatest of all times that's all
flesh but what we spoke about earlier it
was about who's going to make it into
the kingdom of God and who's going to be
punished forever
so man go thing debah go ahead yeah yeah
and the other question is from
Colossians 1 vers 15 and 16 is this
saying the
principalities and Thrones are put in by
God I'm ask in this because does our
vote really
count okay let's read this L that's our
last question anyway tanzel read that
Colossians 1 and pick it up at that 15
and 16 so we can complete our session go
ahead
brother who is the image of the
invisible God the firstborn of every
creature by him were all things created
that are in heaven and are in the earth
visible and invisible whether they be
Thrones or Dominion or principalities or
Powers all things were created by Him
and for
him and a
self-explanatory that's it but anyway
we're going to do some quick scripture
go to Hebrews 1 and
read Hebrews 1 1-3 that's do it
quickly Hebrews 1 1 through3
yep God who at sunry times and th was
man spake in time pass unto the fathers
by the prophets having these last days
spoken unto us by a son whom he have
appointed heir of All Things by whom all
also he made the worlds who being the
brightness of his glory and the
expressed image of his persons and
upholding All Things by the word of his
power when he had by himself purged our
sin sat down on the right hand of the
on
high so the one that's expressed image
look just like him Jesus look just like
the father and right and Jesus the one
that created
everything now skip down to verse 15
first let's go to 1 Corinthians 15
21-23 for Since By Man Came Death by man
came also the resurrection of the Dead
for as in Adam all died even so in
Christ shall all be made alive but every
man in his own order Christ the first
fruits afterwards they that are Christ
at his
coming so Christ is the first born from
the dead he the one that R from the dead
and the rest over to come when he come
one other place Romans 8 28 and
29 yeah
yeah and we know that all things work
together for good to them that love God
to them who are the call according to
his
purpose for whom he did for know he also
did predestinate to be conformed to the
image of his son that he might be the
first born among many
brothers so Jesus the first born from
the dead and he is the beginning
uh uh uh uh being that the uh that the
uh he the first man that died when he
became man and Rose as God it's all that
simple the firstborn of many brothers
the firstborn from the dead he is also
creat and he look just like the father
that's all I have to say yeah and as far
as that last question about uh you
asking about voting that's good you vote
a lot of people paid the ultimate for
you to be able to vote but that's your
choice and voting is not a sin just
wanted to say that too some people think
that voting is a sin so look Jeremiah
wrote a letter to the people in the
first captivity under under
Nebuchadnezzar he said seek the peace of
the city because that is your
peace and how do you do that you try and
vote for the one that you going to give
you more peace yes
sir let you know you got a hand and it's
all that simple yep all right sister
Deborah time check yes the time is
9:03 all right we'd like to thank
everybody all around the world who tuned
in with us this evening we had fun being
a part of you this evening we say that
if you submitted a question and we
didn't have a chance to get to it don't
resubmit it sister Deborah is going to
take it put it in rotation and we will
deal with your question next week we
want to thank you all once again and
until we come together again may you all
be safe may you all be blessed and may
the Lord have mercy on us all close us
out brother tanzel Our Father which are
in heaven Hallowed be thy name thy
kingdom come thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven give us this day our
daily bread and forgive us of our debts
as we forgive our Deb TOs and lead us
not into temptation but Deliver Us from
Evil for thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever in Jesus
name we pray amen